dibru.ac.in 2017-01-19

# Privacy Policy - Dibrugarh University

**About this policy**  
This policy explains what types of personal information will be gathered when you visit the Dibrugarh University's website, and how this information will be used. Please note that this policy applies to the University's main web pages (i.e. those in www.dibru.ac.in).

All colleges, divisions, faculties, departments, schools, centres, academic services, libraries, museums and collections of the University run and maintain their own websites on the dibru.ac.in domain. These sites may carry their own privacy policy or provide additional information relating to their activities, which will supersede or supplement this Privacy Policy. For further information about the structure of the University's web presence, please see About this site.

If you follow a link to any other website, please check their policies before you submit any personal information to those websites.

**Information collected**  
On some parts of the website, you may be asked to provide some limited personal information in order to enable the provision of certain services (e.g. prospectus ordering, registering with a society, applying for a vacancy etc). The University may store this information manually or electronically. By supplying this information you are consenting to the University holding and using it for the purposes for which it was provided. Information provided will be kept for as long as is necessary to fulfil that purpose.

We may also collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our webmasters. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns which does not identify any individual and allows us to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.

**How the information collected is used**  
Personal information provided to the University by you will only be used for the purposes stated when the information is requested. Personal information will not be sold to third parties, or provided to direct marketing companies or other such organisations without your permission.

Demographical and statistical information about user behaviour may be collected and used to analyse the popularity and effectiveness of the University's website. Any disclosure of this information will be in aggregate form and will not identify individual users.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties if we are under a duty to disclose or share such information in order to comply with any legal obligation or to protect the rights, property or safety of the University, its members or others.

**How we use "cookies"**  
Most of our web pages use "cookies". A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we place on your computer or mobile device if you agree. These cookies allow us to distinguish you from other users of our website, which helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allow us to improve our website.

For more detailed information on the cookies we use on the University's main web pages (i.e. those in www.dibru.ac.in) and the purposes for which we use them, please see our Cookie Statement. Please refer to individual web pages for further information about the use of cookies on other web pages on the dibru.ac.in domain.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email.

**Contact**  
Any queries or concerns about privacy on this website should be sent by email to [info@dibru.ac.in](mailto:info@du.ac.in).
